Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Listen to me carefully, Osman Bey.
Be my banner lord.
Shake the world.
You're looking for a dog like Alişar...
not a banner lord.
Balgay says a thing for just once.
And when he says that, he
shakes the world.
Mountains surrender.
Don't you know that we've
opposed to many rulers?
I say that I want every piece
of land including seas.
Every castle, every city and...
Constantine.
Your desires blind many people.
But...
I'll teach you that the blood in my
veins won't bow down to anyone.
How dare you?
How do you think you can order me?
Obey me, Osman.
Obey me so that your Alps...
will batten the smell of blood.
The day I obey you...
will become the day that
Turk's traditions die.
I disregard your traditions.
And I make rugs from corpses...
like you.
Obey...
or die.
Shahada or freedom.
Tell your soldiers to bring us water.
We dried up because we
killed so many of you.
You'll lick the mud on my shoes, Turk.
It'll be enough for you.
Will you be able to say that
when I'm killing you?
Dündar Bey.
My Gündüz.
Uncle! Uncle! Uncle!
Dündar Bey!
Bamsı Bey.
- Where's Osman?
- How's Osman?
He's talking to Balgay. Balgay
wants something from him.
I don't know how to live
with this black destiny.
Shuu up and walk.
Walk!
Be ready.
We'll kill them...
with our weapons.
We'll go with Osman if necessary.
- Be ready.
- Thanks, my Bey.
Wait here.
Die with your Alps or
glorify your soul.
Your decision.
Commander Balgay.
The tents know about you.
Everyone felt Balgay's power.
Go to New Bazaar and...
bring Sheikh Edebalı to me.
Dervishes will be in New Bazaar.
I wanted you to eat something.
And I brought you water.
My Sheikh.
I want to say something if you let me.
I'm guilty.
I went too far.
I didn't listen to you.
I knew but I was late.
Forgive me.
Where is the difference...
between the devil and human, Bala?
Allah created the devil...
to obey Adam.
The devil didn't listen to him.
He sinned.
Allah...
wanted Adam to stay away from
the forbidden fruit.
Adam didn't listen to him.
He sinned.
Both of them...
didn't listen.
The devil was so arrogant but...
Adam swore off.
He apologized.
It's good for humanity.
Allah loves the ones who apologize the
most.
But...
there's people He loves more.
The ones who apologize and
don't repeat the same fault.
What about you, my Sheikh?
Will you forgive me?
We're not forgivers, Bala.
Only Allah forgives.
We only love and tolerate.
And we love you for your honesty.
We love you with your faults.
You're our one and only.
I thank Allah that He filled you
with cleverness...
politeness and clean heart.
We want you to preserve these.
And we want this for you...
not for us.
Father...
I love you.
When you stand away from
me, my heart breaks.
You're the gift and...
entrustment of Allah to me.
Your heart is clean. I know
your intention is good.
From now on...
I'm sure that you'll try not to...
do bad things.
You see, uncle?
We're taken captured in our own land.
This hurts the most.
I couldn't save my brother's entrustments.
I couldn't.
Shahada or freedom.
I'll adorn my weapon out of their corpses.
Catch!
Balgay wants Edebalı.
We have to go to Bazaar. Come on!
Come on!
Allah!
It's hard to serve the guests...
as much as it is to ride
the vicious horse.
I punched you out like a dog...
so that you can enjoy my serve.
Today, that jackal Osman have showed me that...
if I let Turks breathe...
your breathes become...
Mongol blood.
Raise your evil heads!
Gündüz.
Gündüz!
My nephew.
Gündüz...
Now...
tell me, Dündar Bey.
Tell me one thing not to call out
Osman, who didn't obey me.
Gündüz.
Gündüz!
Allah!
- What is it?
- They raided the tribe.
They captured Dündar Bey and Gündüz.
Look what happened to us.
- Help us, my Allah.
Valiants, the day has come.
We killed those cruels back then.
Now, it's time to fight.
Now, it's time to fight with
passion, with love.
Not with anger.
They came here to make my uncle and
my brother obey.
Now, they will obey.
Mongol aims at Edebalı.
However, if they hurt Edebalı, that
means they kill our source of knowledge.
My Osman!
What are we waiting for?
May our swords be blessed.
Allahu-akbar ( Allah is the greatest)
- Allahu-akbar (Allah is the greatest)
Let's go!
Gündüz!
Osman.
Osman is my nephew.
He is young, he is zippy.
We directly question the leader,
shepherd Dündar.
Why didn't you inform your nephew
about Mongols' anger?
We told him, but, he didn't listen.
Gündüz has nothing to do with this.
Don't kill my nephew.
Give me a reason, Dündar.
Just one.
We didn't know it could go this far.
We didn't know Osman would get
out of hand.
Gündüz.
Then, know this.
We came here with our ancestor
Cengiz's flames.
We came here to destroy, to burn.
If you make another mistake, I'll make
a drum...
out of your skin and play it
in the Söğüt square.
Gündüz.
You'll obey me unconditionally, Dündar.
Do you understand me?
Obey.
I will...
I will obey you.
You will bring Osman to me.
That way, you'll show your loyalty.
I will bring Osman...
to you.
I will.
You have three days.
Or, I'll destroy your tribe.
Now, take your nephew and...
go back to your tribe and say:
Mongols have come for good.
Gündüz, Gündüz, my nephew.
Come on, get up.
Come on, Bismillah. (in the name of Allah)
Gündüz, come on.
Get up
- Let's go.
- Take them out.
Kayı's brave women.
Today, we are not going to cry and
sit down.
Today, we stand up and...
show Mongol's the power
of Kayıs!
Inform your sisters, they should take
positions outside.
- We must be ready.
- Eyvallah (Okay) Selcan Hatun.
It's not clear whether our men come
back or not, but...
we know that the only return is to
Allah.
Mongols will arrive at this tent.
And we will show them that we
won't bow them!
Let those dogs see that Kayı Hatuns
fight like Kayı men.
I swear on our ancestors, Oguz's lands...
- We won't bow!
We will present death to those
who want to command Turks!
We will!
- Today, we fight!
- Today, we shahada!
Ahis, who took shelter in Başkonuş plateau,
are ready.
- They will take action with your command.
- Eyvallah (thank you)
Thank them.
- What is it?
- Balgay.
He raided Söğüt with his soldiers,
my Sheik.
He captured Dündar Bey and Gündüz Bey.
He is being cruel.
In Baqarah Surah, My Allah says...
"And We will surely test you with
something of fear..."
"and hunger and a loss of wealth..."
"and lives and fruits..."
"but give good tidings to the patient."
[Baqarah Surah 2:155]
Zülfikar.
Inform Ahis.
We need to take precautions.
Where are we going to go, my Sheik?
Nowhere.
We will stand up.
If this state falls...
it means there is no hope for Muslims.
Mongols! Mongols are coming!
I want Edebalı alive.
Burn the rest.
Come on, friends!
Allahuekber! Allahuekber! (Allah is
the greatest)
My Sheikh!
I want Edebalı alive. Burn the rest.
Osman.
I'm here, my Sheikh!
Allah is eternal!
Alps, we're going!
Protect our Sheikh!
My Bey, protect Sheikh Edebalı.
I'll deal with them.
Come on.
Don't kill him.
I want him alive.
I like you.
You're my cup of tea.
Be careful. I'm made of iron.
Don't break your jaw.
You saved them.
Now tell me. Who will save you?
Allah will.
What were you saying in Alişar's mansion?
I remembered.
"I'm a witness!", you said.
But you didn't witness
everything, Salvador.
For example what my anger can do.
There.
You don't know.
He can still make sounds!
Good.
Princess...
Listen!
Please explain.
I'm listening.
Princess...
You said everything at the mansion!
Now it's time to pay for them.
As I'm bored...
... I'll come here and rip your
fingernails off one by one!
Stop. Stop! Stop!
Princess!
You don't know the big secret!
Are you okay?
Osman sent me here to gather information.
He's waiting for my word.
He... He'll give you the things you want.
Think about it.
Madam, this letter just came.
Mongols.
The letter is from Alişar.
The Mongol commander Balgay will
be our guest, Helen.
This dog...
... should also talk to Master Yannis.
Don't let him die!
I'm the wolf of these mountains,
Osman Bey!
Don't you worry!
Sergeant Samsa.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
( in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
O The Healer!
It's ready, Osman Bey.
Praise be, my valiant! Praise be!
Fate protects one from their death.
You're a godsend.
Thankfully, Allah blessed us with you,
my Sheikh.
Do you think they'll let brother
Konur live, my Bey?
The taste of your blood tells
me that you're brave.
But it's obvious that you're
not smart.
All of you will pay the price for picking
on the Turks!
I ask one question, I expect one answer,
you miserable Turk!
Where is Osman?
You look for him, but he'll find you.
You'll see who the mountain and
who the hill is soon.
Where is Osman?!
He's where you'll die!
They scared everyone.
They discouraged everyone.
They attacked the Tent too.
The same goes for soldiers, doesn't it
Bamsı Bey?
Someone who kills death, who makes
fear kneel...
... who gives hope to his people, is
called a soldier.
Let's see which valiant will shine
during this trial.
Thank you, wise one. Thank you.
Tell me. What is this valiant's quality
that will make him pass this trial?
Not at all. This is a hard question,
Bamsı Bey.
A man is a sufferer. First, he must
know which soil to plant his seed.
He must know in which season he
should plant his seed.
He must know when to water it, and how
to work the soil.
He mustn't give a chance to the wild grass
which don't want the seed to sprout.
While working on all of these...
... he must not lose his love, his
nerve, his sincerity.
One day, the seeds will sprout.
He will harvest them.
The goods will gain value.
That day, this huge garden will not say
"These goods are mine!"
..."They are my labour of love!",
Bamsı Bey.
Whoever has such morals, such devotion...
... My Allah will be that
valiant's friend.
We'll be on their throats today!
Söğüt will be their graves!
We'll take our brother's revenge!
Konur is stiff. He'll stand upright!
He'll hold on!
Sergeant Samsa!
Osman Bey. There's no time to rest.
Let's go and save Konur Alp.
I'm doing fine.
Erkut, what is it?
- New Bazaar's keeper Nizamettin.
- What about him?
He's Yannis' servant, my Bey.
Tell Master Yannis that Edebali's Ahis
will come from Engürü.
Alişar Bey will do what's necessary
so Ahis don't come.
You can go.
I'll dump their bodies in a river.
Tell Master Yannis that his secret
is safe.
Nizamettin!
Hang on, my Dervish. Hang on.
Where is Akça Dervish, son?
I took him to Samsa Bey's Tent, my Sheikh.
He's safe.
Tie Nizamettin's dead body to your horse
and send it so Söğüt.
Send it so they can see who the real
owners of these lands are!
As you wish, my Bey.
- Where's Osman and Edebali?
- They ran away.
That's bad news.
You let the men who'll cause the most
trouble slip through your hands.
No one runs away from the Mongol's
weapon, Alişar.
They'll come out of their
holes eventually.
You don't know them, Cerkutay
They need to be found immediately.
Don't you worry about them?
Commander Balgay is waiting for you.
Pull yourselves together, mother. Aunt!
We can't fight with them!
Only an ambush for that dog
Balgay will shake them.
- As long as there is such a valiant.
- Who's that valiant?
Osman? We had such wise Beys once.
Will Osman save us from
the Mongol thugs now?
In these lands--
My Bey!
Father!
What happened, my Bey?
What do you think happened, Hatun?
The grim reaper is in our Tent.
He'll take lives as he pleases.
I'll eradicate this tumour which is
attacking our lands.
I'll either honour these lands
or I'll die!
We'll follow you wherever you go,
Head Alp.
No, Kongun Alp. No.
I'll sort this one out myself.
You stay by Dündar Bey while I'm not here.
Where's Osman?
He can do whatever he wants.
He's responsible for all of these!
If you did what was necessary,
it wouldn't have happened.
Shut up, Hatun! Shut up!
- I don't want to deal with you too.
- Enough, Dündar Bey!
Are you a valiant to me only?
No one could deal with the Mongols.
How can we?
If it's necessary for the Tent's safety,
give Osman to them!
I can't destroy our families
just for Osman!
Kulucahisar, then Bilecik, Yarhisarı,
and İnegöl governors, Commander Balgay.
I want all of these castles, Alişar.
All their soldiers are well-equipped.
They reinforced their walls.
I say I want Constantinople...
... you show me the broken Byzantine
walls as obstacles.
I have these castles' keys, Balgay.
Sofia?
She's so shameless that she'd sell
her ancestry to protect her lands.
She's waiting for you in the castle.
How will I benefit from her?
Thanks to her, we'll sell our goods in
the Greek markets...
... all the way to Constantinople.
With the goods, your soldiers'
path will be opened.
Step by step. One day they will wake up
and see that their walls are wracked.
Sofia, huh?
Is she beautiful?
Shiny, like the moon. Sleek like
a pillar. Poisonous like a snake.
If you take the wrong turn, you'll be
covered in mud, Alişar.
Do you understand?
I'll carry booty for you, Balgay.
More booty than you ever saw in your life.
Commander Balgay. Osman has sent
a gift for Alişar Bey.
Ears lie, eyes are loyal.
Let's see.
Here, my Sheikh.
Sharpen your swords, everyone!
Today, they took one from us. Tomorrow,
we'll take a thousand from them!
We'll make the Mongols regret
coming to these lands.
I forgot my wounds because
of the pain in my heart.
Let it hurt. Let it hurt.
My flame burns brighter as it hurts!
Those infidels are in our Tent,
and we're in this cave.
- How can one stand this, my Bey?
- Relax.
Our Prophet also hid in a cave
to escape from the infidels.
Don't forget, valiants. There is a
cave Sevr for every truth to hide!
Until the Mongol dogs grip the Turkish
ways, they can't leave these lands!
But... Brother Konur is waiting for us.
- Let's go.
- Stop, son!
Once anger gets into one's heart,
he'll be out of his mind.
- Don't rush!
- My Sheikh!
Bamsı Bey! I can't let them
decide Konur's fate!
- Osman!
- You know the Mongols the best!
They are such snakes that they'll
use Konur to bite you!
During hardships, you solve some problems
with swords in a field...
... you solve others with being
a shadow in a corner.
Bala! Go to the Kayı Tent
with Gonca in disguise.
Your duty is being our eyes in the Tent.
Bamsı Bey. Take Hatuns to the Tent.
I'll tell you what to do.
Thank you, my Osman.
Alişar brought these Mongols here, my Bey!
Alişar will burn in this fire!
He'll burn!
There was a Kayı arrow on
the body, Alişar Bey.
It's certain that Osman did this.
He's behind every trick
and every incident.
I didn't know whom I trusted
these lands with.
Osman! I'll bury you alive!
I'll skin you with my bare hands, I'll
entertain ravens with your screams, Osman!
Who is this?
Manager of New Bazaar Nizamettin.
What does Osman have to do with
a Bazaar officer?
I think his goal is something else,
Commander Balgay.
If that's the case, what are you
waiting for? Go find it out.
What are your thoughts, Alişar Bey?
No one in their right minds can
make sense of what he does.
Didn't I tell you to look after every
branch, every corner...
... every shadow of every Turk?
Balgay! Balgay listen!
Why should I listen to an
imbecile like you?
You got my gold stolen. You brought
Kulucahisar and Kayıs to the brink of war.
Is this how you treat the lands
I trusted you with?
Balgay! Balgay, listen to me!
I'm begging you! Don't to it!
I'm begging you! Don't do it!
If you were my dog, you
couldn't bite my enemy.
I don't want such a servant.
No!
Before you complete...
... the job in Konya, don't you come back!
- Balgay!
- You don't put a stone...
... back to where you took it, Alişar.
If you want to live, bring me some
good news.
- Don't to it, Balgay!
- Are you still here?
For now, the only use of you was
bringing Osman to me.
The days which I'll make him kill
you are near, Alişar.
What does Balgay want from you?
Did he say anything?
He promised to make me the Banner Lord.
His intention is obvious, my Sheikh.
He wants to scare us and loot us.
He thinks that he can make me his ally.
Since he saw that you won't submit to
power, he'll look for new allies.
He'll do it with Alişar.
Alişar will take Balgay to
the castle for sure.
The sides have become clear, son.
Dogs with dogs...
... wolfs with wolfs!
Welcome, Commander Balgay.
Out of my way, imbecile!
Stop!
Princess Sofia is waiting for you.
Here.
White like the moon, sleek
like a pillar...
... poisonous like a snake Sofia.
Is that you?
Mighty Mongol Commander Balgay.
Welcome to my castle.
I thought Alişar Bey was also coming.
I sent Alişar to Konya.
But I didn't come empty-handed,
Princess Sofia.
Yergutay.
Nizamettin had been working
for you for a while.
How did you come up with that,
Commander Balgay?
What do I have to do with Alişar's
life long...
... servant Nizamettin?
Shut up!
Until Osman sent this dog's dead
body as a gift...
... Alişar who is as dumb as a
bird didn't know anything.
Until I solved it with my mind.
Akça Dervish was your biggest enemy
Edebali's man.
Alişar was licking that old man's boots
just so he could be with his daughter.
It's certain he didn't make them do it.
They don't call you the mighty
Commander for nothing.
Why did you want to make your spy
kill the Dervish, Sofia?
Did he see something you were hiding in
Alişar's mansion or did he see anyone?
Edebali is our enemy as much as
he's your enemy.
Our common enemies will make
agreeing with you easier.
I didn't come here to make an agreement.
I came here to make you
my bondwoman(Female servant)!
Not in Kulucahisar...
... I'll let you make me your
bondwoman in Constantinople.
Balgay.
I like you.
You are an intelligent woman.
You are ambitious...
...charming and determined.
I had the table prepared for you.
After you.
Only the Byzantine cockroaches eat on a
table.
A Mongolian who eats at a table is
an open target for his enemies.
I came here to talk about
business...
... or to destroy your castle.
Söğüt has four gates.
Balgay put his guards here.
And we will infiltrate from there...
... from behind the Bazaar to this
point.
Understood, Osman Bey.
But this means we have to fight our way
to exit.
Those locusts will attack us as soon as
one of them smells us.
Boran.
Söğüt is our earned right.
It doesn't matter if clash against Genghis
Khan or Balgay. We'll win.
After the Mongolians, we will show the
whole world that blood is what they get...
...when they mess with the Turks.
What do you want from your
Princess Sofia, Commander Balgay?
As a result of my negotiating skills,
along with the every beauty inside...
...I took over the control of Kulacahisar.
This castle is mine now.
Now you'll give me the other
governor's castles.
Do you understand?
Exceedingly.
Since Balgay's strong hands...
... know where to take me...
It is my duty to...
...serve the hand that I
could not bend.
Along with my soldiers, I'm ready to obey
with my flesh and soul, Commander Balgay.
Then, I raise my sword that has been
washed with Turkish blood...
... for my Queen.
Ayşe!
I can no longer stand the responsibilities
of Zöhre. Dündar Bey...
... is a coward himself.
They blame my Osman for everything.
They think if Osman had obeyed Alişar just
like they did...
... none of these would happen.
There is no way Osman would allow the
honor of Kayı lay on the ground.
What are we going to do?
If we don't do anything...
...they will hand Osman to the Mongolians.
We have three days.
May Allah be with us.
My aunt.
How are you, Selcan Hatun.
How we are is basically a Tent that
submits to the power of the Mongols.
There are no news from my Osman.
My heart feels like it is on fire.
Don't worry, Sercan Hatun.
Osman is fine.
You don't say!
Where is he?
I hope his condition is alright.
I will tell you everything.
Now tell me. What is going on?
Balgay wants my Osman.
Dündar won't say anything against it.
He is okay with giving Osman away.
He gave us three days, Bala Hatun.
He said he will burn down the Tent
if Osman doesn't come back in three days.
You stay here my dear.
I will tell them news.
You should leave, Gonca.
There is no time to waste.
Osman is holding his ground with Edebali.
With the help of Allah, they will defeat
the Mongols.
We will either walk on our path free or
recite the Kalima Shahadah.
If Allah allows us.
However, nobody can know that I was here.
Don't you worry, my beautiful girl.
You came here and calmed our worried
minds.
Because of you my heart is finally at
peace.
Alişar has fallen from the game.
Now, the new King is Balgay.
Don't you ever forget that even a simple
pawn can beat the King, Sofia.
Checkmate.
Osman is now a living dead.
If he doesn't surrender, Balgay will
destroy the whole Tent.
Edebali has left the Bazaar.
As soon as Balgay finds them, he will
take their heads.
Now, there is not even a single branch
that Ahis can hold.
However, there is one thing. Father.
How are we going to get rid of Balgay?
Everyone has a weakness, my daughter.
And I know Balgay's weakness the best.
Where are you going to go, father?
It's time I pay a visit to Balgay.
Thanks to you, now we know what exactly he
wants.
You are going to give him what he wants.
May God protect you, Master Yannis.
Dündar Bey.
Ever since you became in charge of the
Tent...
...there is nothing but trouble.
Now, the Mongols are here.
What do those tyrants want my Bey?
They gave us three days.
They want to capture Osman.
All of these oppressions and torments we
are going through.
Does Osman worth it?
Let's hand him and be done with them
already.
Don't talk as if you are giving away
a sheep from your herb.
Osman is the only thing that my father
left me.
What about our children?
What about them, Gündüz Bey?
A Bey always takes care after his Tent no
matter what.
Not only Osman but also I would not give
even a single cloth piece from this Tent.
Are we going to sacrifice the whole Tent
for Osman?
It's not about Osman!
It's about our freedom!
Why can't you understand?
Then you better get this, Gündüz Bey.
A certain herb does not feed on freedom
and empty promises.
How can we let our enemy walk freely in
our own land?
We are the Kayıs!
We shout "Freedom!" to these mountains,
and they shout back "Allahu Akbar!"
What kind of an intimidation this is?
You bloodless!
Enough!
Enough.
How childish of you!
This is not who we are.
Behave yourselves!
You are all acting like Beys...
...as if you can't see there is already a
Bey here at his council.
Sit down! All of you!
It is not the time we sit but the time we
do what our customs dictate, Dündar bey.
Tell us your last decision already so
that we can understand your motive.
My decision is as obvious as the wildness
of the Mongols.
Especially since our customs strongly
dictate we need to stand together.
We'll wait for Osman and try not to end
in such conflicts again.
What if he doesn't come back, Dündar Bey?
While you constantly worry about your
children...
...we are always sure of ours, Demirci
Bey.
Sometimes, Osman might be a bit crazy
and full of youth.
However, he knows what he is doing.
He would never leave his Tent alone.
Not even a single second he would
hesitate to help his people.
No matter what, he would grab his sword
and find a way to help.
Is our old friend here?
He will arrive soon sir.
One of the Margaret monks, Yannis.
It's been years.
You see? Finally we meet once again.
I came here to put an end to our
unfinished business.
Sheikh Edebali.
We will kill him just like how we killed
Ahi Evran together.
What did you bring me, Yannis?
What are these names?
Who are they?
Bilecik, Inegöl, and Harmankaya.
Names of all monks and people who
are devoted to me...
...and live at these very casttles.
Some of them are castle commanders.
Some of them are soldiers.
Some of them are doctors.
Cooks.
Stablemen.
With a single order from me, they will be
ready to serve you.
What is the reason behind this, Yannis?
For my daughter.
Your daughter?
Sofia!
I came here to present you...
...a very beautiful Princess...
...along with Constantinople, Balgay.
Our ancestors told us to eat high
quality meat always...
...and to listen to the words of old men.
If I don't like the meat you serve with
your daughter...
...both of you will drown in my puke,
Yannis.
Don't you ever forget this.
To his almighty Genghis Khan...
...and his breed.
They keep Konur inside the church.
My Bey.
They are probably waiting for us.
You should wait here.
I will go rescue Konur and come back.
However, we might have to clash as
soon as we are out.
We need to stay alert, my brothers.
Understood, Samsa Bey.
Konur!
Where have you been, Osman bey?
Drop your swords!
Osman Bey, it's an ambush!
Be careful, my Osman Bey.
I will choke all of you on your own blood.
You are not different from our past foes
whom we fed our dogs with.
Come at me!
Leave this place, Osman Bey!
Find Osman!
Stop!
It's the end of the road, Balgay.
Come.
And fight.
Do you know what happens when a dog acts
like a wolf, son of Dündar?
He will be executed in front of other
dogs...
...so that they can learn their lessons.
Commander Balgay.
Osman has just fled.
However, his Alps are our prisoners now.
He will come back for his dogs.
We will go this time, Kongar.
We will have a blood fest at Kayı's Tent.
They will learn to surrender.
What did they do to you, Konur brother?
Your face is barely recognizable.
Is that so?
I don't agree.
I feel like a lion.
A lion?
More like a wounded lion.
Stop messing with me, Sergeant Samsa.
My brother has always been like a lion.
Nothing can harm him.
I'm not real lion around here.
He is the real lion.
My dear brother.
To Pharaohs, cruels, infidels, he once
again showed us how to stand...
... against our enemies with bravery,
not with our bulk.
My lion.
What's wrong, Abdurrahman brother?
You seem dreamy again.
We learned how to fight like a real man...
...what it means to be brothers in arms...
...from those like you whose beard turned
to gray...
...because of fighting non-stop
for his Tent.
I drifted away.
I just fear that a valiant like
Osman Bey...
...might be captivated because of us.
May Allah not allow that, Abdurrahman
brother.
Amin.
Samsa Bey.
What are we going to do now?
Don't get nervous, my Boran.
La Ghalib illa Allah.
(There is no victor/conqueror except God)
Amin.
Didn't we promise...
...that as long as we are alive and we
have our swords with us...
...we won't become exhausted...
...hopeless...
...or afraid of anything...
...that we will never surrender and die
if it is necessary to protect our Tent.
Didn't we, Konur Brother?
Huh, Boran Brother?
Yes, we all promised that.
We did, Sergeant Samsa.
Let the tyrants be tyrants.
Let them be a kind of nightmare.
Let them slay every single one of us.
What is important is to know that our
blood, swords, and words...
...can not be changed.
After all, we can't change our destiny.
There is nothing but to
accept the shahada, Allah's power.
Allahu Akbar!
My friends.
Listen to me carefully now.
Gonca Hatun.
You ought to tell me!
How's the Tent doing?
It's doing bad, Osman Bey.
It's doing bad.
It wants you back.
Dündar Bey had to submit to others.
If you don't surrender in three days.
We lost everything, my Sheikh.
Osman!
All of Söğüt is under attack.
They raided every Tent there is.
All Beys are taken prisoners.
Osman!
They got my Alps as well.
Stand up!
I want to tell you an anecdote.
An anecdote from Battle of Uhud.
So that you can understand what real
responsibility and hope mean.
That day when Muslims and non-believers
started to clash...
...do you think all that was easy?
Almost three hundred soldiers left
our prophet's side.
His cheek was wounded by a sword dash.
His lips got torn by the stones...
...and some of his teeth got
broken.
After another sword dash...
...blood was
dripping from his blessed forehead.
While he was going back to Mecca...
...he fell into one of
the ditches dug by the heathens.
His knee was torn this time.
He lost too many comrades.
He even lost...
...the lion of Allah...
...his uncle, Hamza,...
...on that battle.
After everything that happened to him.
He could still say that...
''My Rab please have mercy on them.''
''They don't know about the truth.''
Do you know why all of these happened, my
son?
Because...
... some of his soldiers...
... did not complete his orders.
The believers who had seen the heathens
flee away...
... left their spot too soon
to get their loot.
Don't you forget, my son.
This anecdote is one of the most important
doctrines of archaic history of Islam.
When the believers are scattered around...
... the heathens will start to riot.
Now, your duty is...
...not to scatter around but to pull
yourself and everything together.
Now, Kayı Tent is that spot where the
believers left too soon.
If we leave the spot...
... the heathens will try to strike more
stronger than ever.
Now claim your Tent...
...your people and your cause...
...stronger than ever.
So that the Muslims can riot against the
heathens once again.
I am flattered and full of hope again, my
Sheikh.
Gonca Hatun.
You better listen to me carefully.
Go to the Tent to my aunt Selcan.
Traitors!
You are all traitors!
Allah!
- Batur!
- Brother!
Let go of me, Bey!
Hatun!
Here is Cengiz Han's soul!
Balgay is here!
My Allah.
Stand tall, my lions! Don't make the enemy
happy! Stand tall!
Now...
We will...
make these dogs obey!
Allah!
Don't bow to the cruel!
Come on, brothers, alps!
Hold on!
Allah!
The truth is the same with a sharp knife.
I brought you the captivity.
May you strengthen us, my Allah.
Amin.
Obviously, you forgot.
I'll make it clear.
We will cut the head that doesn't obey
Mongols.
How am I going to get out of this
situation, my Allah?
Give me power to destroy my enemy
Help my brothers.
I wonder what you are up to, Sıddık.
I told you you'd go through a challenging
task.
Are you ready?
What do you order, Osman Bey?
Command me.
You are going to betray me.
Help me, my Allah.
Help me.
You have been following me.
Did you think that I wouldn't notice you?
Who are you?
You'll find out, Osman Bey.
Today, the fortified crescent will
brighten up, Osman Bey.
Your time has come.
Dündar.
Ah Dündar.
Dündar, who keeps silent while his
Alps are being tortured.
You ruined my Ertuğrul Bey's entrustment.
No, no. Bamsı Bey can't keep silent
to this cruelty.
What are you doing Bamsı Bey?
They are looking for you everywhere.
I prefer dying to keep silent,
Selcan Hatun.
We are not dead yet, thanks to Allah.
Follow me.
Bala.
Gonca Hatun.
Bala Hatun, is it ready?
Osman Bey didn't leave his alps to
Balgay's hand, Bamsı Bey.
My Ertuğrul Bey's entrustment is in
good hands, Bamsı Bey. We won't give up.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate)
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
We don't have the answers, Osman Bey.
You'll get the answers inside.
Enter if you are ready.
Is this dog responsible for these?
Let go of my brother, you ignoble!
Stand back, fool, stand back so that...
you don't die under my feet like
a bug.
I'll make you regret, Balgay.
You'll be drowned of the blood you shed
because of your cruelty.
Seeing your outfit, you are a hatun of
tradition.
But, it is obvious that you don't know me.
They call me Mongol's iron-fist Bangal!
I'll make lakes out of blood,
mountains out of bones!
The fire rises where I go!
This glorious tent has been a grave to the
cruel, Balgay.
You will be one of them too.
Your greed wakens my anger.
Blue-eyed son.
As a warning to others, I will...
I will...
Kill you slowly.
Help us, my Allah.
Fame Kayı Bey Sergeant Samsa.
Hosshht!
You'll die like a dog.
Ertugrul's famous servant.
Don't.
Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Ignoble dog!
Don't.
You will all watch what happens to those
who don't obey Mongols.
- No, no no!
- Wait!
Let him go.
Leave my son alone.
Leave him alone.
Your hatuns are courageous as well as
your men.
Balgay likes courageous men and women.
Are those women diligent as well as
being courageous?
Let's see.
Bring me food and Kumis(drink).
I prefer dying to serve you.
Then, watch me drinking this son's blood
instead of Kumis.
No.
No!
Wait!
I'll bring.
Cut me meat.
Don't linger!
Aunt.
Don't.
Aunt, don't!
You'll die, Balgay!
Who are you?
We are the Almighty Sycamore's Turks,
Osman Bey.
We got in flames in Ergenekon, and
We burnt the whole world in Malazgirt.
And now we came here to open a way
from Ötüken to Söğütlü.
I haven't heard of you until now.
We show up in the most difficult times.
We came to brighten up your way with
our ancestor Oguz's light.
My father's dagger.
Masha Allah (praise be!)
Both of your father Ertuğrul Gazi and your
grandfather Süleyman Shah...
was in our society, son.
Now, our crescents point at you.
Turks' latest state Seljuq Empire has
been destroyed by Mongols.
However, hopelessness is not in tradition.
In this country, where we have come thanks
to our tradition...
the situation is bad.
We don't serve to servants.
We obey no one.
However...
The cruelty is all around us.
Our people are about to be out of hope.
Contrarily, the Turk's hope is the
country, son.
This hope sent your father Ertuğrul Gazi
to this country.
Until the sky falls, until the ground
cracks, every Turk is a state.
So, even if a city falls,
the tradition stands still.
Eyvallah, Eyvallah (thanks) but...
Balgay conquered everywhere.
Mongols celebrate the victory in
Turk tribes!
We are here for this.
Bury your sorrow to the hope.
And, remember, Osman Bey.
There can't be Turks without azan,
freedom, and a state!
The power that will stop Balgay is in this
chest.
Balgay liked you.
Drink.
Or I'll make you drink that son's blood.
- No!
Hey, my Allah, who is the owner
of the ground and sky.
This community, this state is yours.
May we don't bow to the cruels.
May fear don't capture our hearts,
my Allah.
Give me power to resurrect this state!
Make Turks rule this age!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com